

CONTACT



hamdanrobbi@gmail.com



+6282131630104



Pungging - Mojokerto

SKILLS

Web Developer Mobile/Android Developer UI/UX Database Analyst (Business/Systems) **Basic Computing English** Networking

PERSONALITY

Discipline

Responsible

Honest

Friendly

HOBBY

Technology

Analyst

Coding

Football

Reading

HAMDAN DZIKRUROBBI

ABOUT ME

My name is Hamdan Dzikrurobbi, I am an active colleger in Telkom University. As a Information System students, i got a lot of experience in a Bussiness Analyst, System Analyst, Programming, Networking, Problem Solving, and Critical Thinking. Other than these Hardskill, i have a lot of Softskill from the Organization, Laboratory, and the Event Committee. An Leadership, Speaking up, Teamwork, Self Management, Communication and the other softskill i gained so far from these activity that i joined.

PERSONAL DETAILS

Date of Birth : Mojokerto, 30 April 1999

Religion : Islam

: Belum Menikah **Status** : hamdan_dz Instagram Linkedin : hamdan-dz

: ead-dzi.herokuapp.com Web

FORMAL EDUCATION

2005 - 2011 SDIT Al-Anwar

2011 - 2014 SMP Negeri 1 Mojosari

2014 - 2017 SMA Negeri 1 Krian

2017 - now Telkom University (Sistem Informasi)

NON FORMAL EDUCATION

2005 - 2011

2012 - 2017 Madrasah Diniyah Al-Amin

WORK EXPERIENCE

2019 - now

Freelance (Data Entry, Web Programming, Teaching in laboratory)

ORGANIZATION EXPERIENCE

Dec 2017 - Dec 2019

Apr 2018 - Dec 2019

Jan 2018 - now

May 2019 - now

Al-Fath Telkom University

ISLAH

HMSI

EAD Laboratory